import 'package:quiz_app/questionQuizModel.dart';

List<QuestionQuizModel?>? questionsQuiz = [
  QuestionQuizModel(
      correctAnswer: "JavaScript Object Notation",
      options: [
        "JavaScript Standard Output Network",
        "JavaScript Object Notation",
        "JavaScript Output Name",
        "Java Source Open Network",
      ],
      question: "1.JSON stands for ?"),
  QuestionQuizModel(
      correctAnswer: "data",
      options: [
        "data",
        "object",
        "Array",
        "string",
      ],
      question: "2.Which of the following is not a type in JSON?"),
  QuestionQuizModel(
      correctAnswer: "Douglas Crockford",
      options: [
        "Douglas Crockford",
        "Rasmus Lerdorf",
        "Douglas Michel",
        "Dennis Michel",
      ],
      question: "3.Who is the Father of JSON?"),
  QuestionQuizModel(
      correctAnswer: "Yes,if it is escaped like (\")",
      options: [
        "No,you should use single quotes",
        "Yes,if you use the ascii code",
        "Yes,if it is escaped like (\")",
        "Yes,you can use it without any special treatment",
      ],
      question: "4.Can you use a double quote inside a JSON string?"),
  QuestionQuizModel(
      correctAnswer: "keys and Values",
      options: [
        "Arrays and Objects",
        "keys and Values",
        "Class and Objects",
        "None of above",
      ],
      question: "5.What are two main structures compose JSON?"),
  QuestionQuizModel(
      correctAnswer: "Using Unicode",
      options: [
        "Using Unicode",
        "Using Keys",
        "Using Datatype",
        "Using Lang"
      ],
      question: "6.How do JSON provide internationalization?"),
  QuestionQuizModel(
      correctAnswer: "Double quote",
      options: [
        "Double quote",
        "Single quote",
        "Both 1&2",
        "None of These",
      ],
      question: "7.JSON strings have used in?"),
  QuestionQuizModel(
      correctAnswer: "To send and receive bits of data.",
      options: [
        "To store information remotely.",
        "To store information locally.",
        "To send and receive bits of data.",
        "All of the Above",
      ],
      question: "8.What is the common usage of JSON on modern websites?"),
  QuestionQuizModel(
      correctAnswer: "comma",
      options: [
        "line break",
        "semi-colon",
        "comma",
        "white space",
      ],
      question: "9.JSON elements are separated by the "),
  QuestionQuizModel(
      correctAnswer: "JSON with padding",
      options: [
        "JSON Parsing",
        "JSON Procedures",
        "JSON Programming",
        "JSON with padding",
      ],
      question: "10.JSONP stands for-"),
];
